Apologies, my little bike, I must've had a mental block; I turned your fuel tap left, not right, I really am a big daft cock.
Oh Little Honda, thou art sick; The invisible shite that lurks in the tank Has stilled thy joyful crank And left you dead to my kick. #Arse
Real toast has now arrived, so that wasn't a stroke or heart attack. But thank you for your concern. #Fuggers
A woman somewhere outside my office window just shouted 'Gosh, that's a massive one, but I don't think it's real'. What happened?
I smell toast approaching. How lucky am I? #SpreadWithTrueLove
I tried making my own hand-cooked crisps, but I just couldn't get my hands hot enough.
I saw 'walled-garden herbs' on a menu last night. I think this trumps 'line-caught' or 'shade-grown'. Any advances? #DustedWithHorseshit
Here you go then. Little Honda. #TheEnd http://t.co/D3gpB3fDfj
Bmw's big K1, Funny looking bike, that one. Fairing's meant to cleave the air, But taking it off's a right 'mare. #BloodyGermans
Deep black is my Honda's frame It gleams, and yet the same Rich darkness does another dark conceal; Our grief. In motion only are we free.
Little Honda, little Honda, Wouldn't want to trouble you With journeys long and luggage large; I'll take the BMW. #Pathetic
Bloody hell, this is good. #French @ozclarke
Fuggit. I'm opening a bottle.
Elephants could never be the size of mice because we don't have currant buns small enough. #CannotKickThisHangover
So: do you want to see a picture of Little Honda? #Yes #NoFugginWay Delete as appropriate and return to this address
Ironically, a leopard-print T-shirt will make you look a right donkey. #AnimalMisappropriation
Zebras have a price if you point a bar-code reader at them. #Fact
If dolphins didn't have noses they'd just look like wonky aeroplanes.
Horses look wrong without people on them, and so do the cabs of articulated lorries when they aren't pulling a trailer.
Giraffes would look idiotic if their legs were really short. #HungOver
Cats would look really weird if they didn't have any ears. #JusSayin
Honda, little Honda, that You still work is kinda spooky. I love you and all that, but today, Iâ€™m off out on the big Suzuki. #Disloyal
Round and round the roundabout, The little Honda ran. In fits and starts, with feeble farts, Emitted by its can. #EspeciallyPoor
Yes, label, obviously. #Specs
Workshop supplies. Risk of terrible cock-up. #ReadLable http://t.co/SVnw37GDr3
Little Honda, Small and simple, Disarming, like A loved one's dimple. #StillEarly
Kawasaki H2 triple, Drunken weave and two-stroke tipple, Little Honda runs so fine But bangs just once for six of thine. #Rubiyat
Little Honda, Drum-braked front, Pretty woman, Hatchback shunt. #True
Honda, Honda, gleaming bright, In the garage, on the right. Enter left a careless man, Who dings you with the watering can. #AABB
Thanks Kiev, for the welcome. #ÑÐ¿Ð°ÑÐ¸Ð±Ñ–
Little Honda, In a race, Open helmet, Making duckface. #NoSelfie
Little Honda, Spokes 'n' shit, Like, really old, But cool, innit? #DaBike
Massive Beemer, massive Beemer; Down below the tank, Opposing pistons, east and west, United at the crank. #Deep
I have a little Honda bike, Of pistons it has one. One pot, one plug, one coil, one carb, 'Tis singularly fun. #MuseHasFled